[
    {
        "front": "つづけます||",
        "back": "continue",
        "chapter": 31
    },
    {
        "front": "みつけます|| ",
        "back": "find",
        "chapter": 31
    },
    {
        "front": "とります| [やすみを～]",
        "back": "take [a holiday]",
        "chapter": 31
    },
    {
        "front": "うけます||［しけんを～］ ",
        "back": "take [an examination]",
        "chapter": 31
    },
    {
        "front": "もうしこみます|",
        "back": "apply for, enter for",
        "chapter": 31
    },
    {
        "front": "きゅうけいします||| ",
        "back": "take a break, take a rest",
        "chapter": 31
    },
    {
        "front": "れんきゅう ",
        "back": "consecutive holidays",
        "chapter": 31
    },
    {
        "front": "さくぶん ",
        "back": "essay, composition",
        "chapter": 31
    },
    {
        "front": "はっぴょう",
        "back": "announcement, presentation (～します: announce)",
        "chapter": 31
    },
    {
        "front": "てんらんかい",
        "back": "exihibition",
        "chapter": 31
    },
    {
        "front": "けっこんしき ",
        "back": "wedding ceremony",
        "chapter": 31
    },
    {
        "front": "[を]そうしき*",
        "back": "funeral",
        "chapter": 31
    },
    {
        "front": "しき*",
        "back": "ceremony",
        "chapter": 31
    },
    {
        "front": "ほんしゃ ",
        "back": "head office",
        "chapter": 31
    },
    {
        "front": "してん ",
        "back": "branch office",
        "chapter": 31
    },
    {
        "front": "きょうかい ",
        "back": "church",
        "chapter": 31
    },
    {
        "front": "だいがくいん",
        "back": "graduate school",
        "chapter": 31
    },
    {
        "front": "どうぶつえん",
        "back": "zoo",
        "chapter": 31
    },
    {
        "front": "おんせん ",
        "back": "hot spring, spa",
        "chapter": 31
    },
    {
        "front": "かえり",
        "back": "return",
        "chapter": 31
    },
    {
        "front": "おこさん",
        "back": "(someone else's) child",
        "chapter": 31
    },
    {
        "front": "ーごう",
        "back": "(train number, typhoon number, etc.)",
        "chapter": 31
    },
    {
        "front": "～のほう",
        "back": "place toward ~, direction of ~",
        "chapter": 31
    },
    {
        "front": "ずっと ",
        "back": "the whole time",
        "chapter": 31
    },
    {
        "front": "※バリ",
        "back": "Bali (Indonesian Island)",
        "chapter": 31
    },
    {
        "front": "※ピカソ",
        "back": "Pablo Picasso, Spanish (1881-1973)",
        "chapter": 31
    },
    {
        "front": "※のぞみ",
        "back": "name of a Shinkansen train (~42 ごう: Nozomi Superexpress No. 42)",
        "chapter": 31
    },
    {
        "front": "※しんこうべ",
        "back": "name of a station in Hyogo prefecture",
        "chapter": 31
    },
    {
        "front": "のこります| ",
        "back": "remain, be left, stay behind",
        "chapter": 31
    },
    {
        "front": "にゅうがくしけん",
        "back": "entrance examination",
        "chapter": 31
    },
    {
        "front": "つきに ",
        "back": "per month",
        "chapter": 31
    }
]